Guide to the Hospitality Leadership: The Cornell Hotel School research papers, 1920-1999.
Hospitality Leadership The Cornell Hotel School research papers
- Hazing of the Hotelies sidebar, Greenbrier sidebar 2, Dick Ferris sidebar, Treatment of Female Hotelies sidebar, None; New Article, Copy No. of pieces: 4 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  Additional description: sidebars to be included in the HH Book
  Recipient: N/A
- Hazing of Hotelies Sidebar, None; New Article, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  Additional description: Sidebar included in HH Book on page 52
  Author: Hazing of Hotelies Sidebar
  Recipient: HH Book
- Dick Ferris Sidebar / Treatment of Female Hotelies Sidebar, None; New Article, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  Additional description: Sidebars included in HH book on pages 140 and 50.
- Photocopied check from Richard Ferris and Underwriter Commitment Form / List of member of the Cornell Society of Hotelmen, 10/15/1995; Memo, Copy No. of pieces: 3 (Box 2, Folder 134)
- Handwritten notes and names. / Copy of check and underwriter commitment form for Chuck LaForge, None; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: 2 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  Author: None / F. G. Marcham?
- Public Affairs Inquiry System, 10/31/1995; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 3 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  Additional description: Information printout on underwriters Erik Hansen, Joseph Lavin, and Leslie Stern
- Public Affairs Inquiry System, 10/31/1995; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 5 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  Additional description: Information printout on underwriters James Butler, Richard Fors, Kenneth and Linda Hamlet, and John Kline
- Chapter 6: "A Bridge Between the Generations", 07/29/1995; 03/10/1961; None; New Article, Copy No. of pieces: 3 (Box 2, Folder 138)
  Additional description: second drafts of chapter 6 and the preface. / poem by Howard Meek
  Author: None / Howard Meek
- Memorandum of Conversation by Dick Kennedy and George Bantuvanis RE: Don Buch's letter about History Book / Re: Hotel School History Book Drafts / None, 07/20/1995; 07/15/1995; None; Memo, No. of pieces: 3 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  Additional description: Correspondence about Book (2)/ Picture Captions for Book
  Author: Kennedy, Dick and Bantuvanis, George / Buch, Don / Unknown
  Recipient: Marcham, John / Chiu, Michael / None
- Hotel History Captions, 8/11/1995; Pamphlet, Copy No. of pieces: 9 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  Additional description: Photo Captions
- Various correspondences about HH Book, 09/08/1995; 09/24/1995; 09/11/1995; 09/02/1995; Memo, Copy No. of pieces: 5 (Box 2, Folder 141)
- Letter format--style questions about HH Book, Various; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 4 (Box 2, Folder 142)
  Additional description: 07/20/1995; 08/11/1995; 09/24/1995; 05/07/1995; 11/06/1995
  Recipient: Brad, Ira, Phil
- Hotel History Captions / Memorandum / "What is a hotelier?"; "A Society for All Hotelies", 8/11/95; 12/05/1995; None; 12/12/1995; Memo, Copy No. of pieces: 11 (Box 2, Folder 143)
  Additional description: List / memo about HH Book acknowledgement section / sidebar explaining what a hotelier is / Hotel Society sidebar
  Author: None / Bill Caruso / John Foote / None
  Recipient: None / Michael Chiu / None / None
- Public Affairs Inquiry System, 11/20/1995; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 11 (Box 2, Folder 144)
  Additional description: Information and Check copies from underwriters
- Letter, copy of check, Public Affairs Inquiry, Underwriter Commitment Form regarding David Bently, 11/21/1995; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 4 (Box 2, Folder 145)
  Recipient: Marjorie
- Curriculum Vitae / "Top Hotel Chiefs from US, Europe and Asia to Discuss Industry's Future at Cornell" / None / None, 04/1985; 02/21/1989; 11/14/1995; Unknown; Memo, Copy No. of pieces: 6 (Box 2, Folder 146)
  Additional description: Cullen's April 1985 resume. / Cornell University News article. / Letter regarding middle initials. / handwritten notes
  Author: Cullen, Thomas / Kaff, Al / Marcham, John / Unknown
  Recipient: None/ n/a / Marjorie / None
- copy of photo of members of the Student Committee for Continuous Improvement, fall of 1995; list of people in photo; handwritten notes about the photo, None; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 3 (Box 2, Folder 147)
- Letter with a copy of letters sent to underwriters, along with a list of additional underwriters to add., 11/27/1995; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 3 (Box 2, Folder 148)
  Author: Tribaldos Jr., Cesar
  Recipient: Marjorie Sharpsteen
- Letter sent to History committee members along with notes on Book, 12/5/1995; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 2, Folder 149)
  Recipient: History committee member
- Copies of faxed memos regarding the title of the Hotel History Book, 08/06/1995; 07/31/1995; Memo, Copy No. of pieces: 3 (Box 2, Folder 150)
  Author: George Bantuvanis
  Recipient: Marcham, John / Chiu, Michael; Kennedy, Richard; Brown, Richard; Marcham, John
- Various correspondences regarding the HH Book, Various dates in 1995; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 9 (Box 2, Folder 151)
- Letter, 4/5/1995; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: None (Box 2, Folder 152)
  Recipient: History committee
- Sidebar for HH Book, 6/24/1995; New Article, Original No. of pieces: 4 (Box 2, Folder 153)
- 2 memos; one regarding the acknowledgement to be written for the underwriters, the other about getting more information about potential underwriters. Also, there are two lists of past presidents of the Cornell Society of Hotelmen, and a list of underwriters., 09/11/1995; 10/29/1995; Memo, Original No. of pieces: 6 (Box 2, Folder 154)
  Author: Chiu, Michael / Marcham, John
  Recipient: Marcham, John / Marjorie
- The first three letters are notes on Various editing/writing problems with the book from presumed proofreaders; the fourth is a letter to one of the proofreaders (Lattin) thanking him for his suggestions., Various; Letter, Original No. of pieces: 4 (Box 2, Folder 155)
  Additional description: 06/13/1995; 02/24/1995; 03/14/1995; 03/14/1995
  Author: Unknown / Shellenberger, Susan / Kiethen, J. / Kennedy, Richard
  Recipient: Marcham, John / Marcham, John / Kennedy, Richard / Lattin, Gerald
- The first two letters list corrections that need to be made to the first draft of the book. The third one is Marcham talking about the corrections that he has received so far., 01/16/1995; 12/19/1994; 03/29/1995; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 3 (Box 2, Folder 156)
  Author: Munster, Rudolf / Chiu, Michael / Marcham, John
  Recipient: Marcham, John / Marcham, John / Brad, Phil, and Ira
- The first letter to the HH readers is asking them to proofread the attached photo captions. The second one is asking them to proofread the last chapter of the book. The next document is a schedule for a HH Book meeting. The other two are correspondence about suggestions/corrections for the book., Various; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 5 (Box 2, Folder 157)
  Additional description: 06/01/1995; 09/23/1995; Unknown; 05/05/1995; 05/10/1995
  Recipient: Hotel History reader (2) / None / Phil and Brad / Brad and Ira
- random pages, from notes on changes to be made on chapter 7 to correspondence about underwriters to part of a story about Dean Meek., 05/14/1995; 09/02/1995; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 4 (Box 2, Folder 158)
- Letter explaining the attached list of photos, when they were taken, and who's in them., 9/21/1995; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 3 (Box 2, Folder 159)
- random notes, some typed, some handwritten. Business card from William Caruso, Unknown; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: 4 (Box 2, Folder 160)
- Hotel History, next edit and production steps / Short-term and long-term schedule / None / None, 04/30/1995; 08/02/1995; 08/02/1995; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 4 (Box 2, Folder 161)
  Additional description: 1st two are schedules and steps for the coming months. The two letters are about the schedules, drafts, what to do.
  Author: Marcham, John?
  Recipient: None / None / Sue / Michael (Chiu), Dick (Kennedy), Dick (Brown), and George (Bantuvanis)
- DeWitt Historical Society Operating Budget / None, Various; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 6 (Box 2, Folder 162)
  Additional description: Budget plan for DeWitt Historical Society, correspondence between Brad and Marcham, List of sidebars
- 4 are letters about drafts of the book, getting a lawyer to review book for libel, deadlines, etc. The last one is about the outline of the project scope., Various; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 5 (Box 2, Folder 163)
  Additional description: 07/15/1995; 06/19/1995; 06/19/1995; Various; 06/16/1995
  Author: Marcham, John (4) / Chiu, Michael
  Recipient: Bob / Dean Dittman / Burt, Robyn / Various / History Book Committee Members
- Third Progress Report, 12/1/1983; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 2, Folder 164)
  Additional description: Rough draft of 1st chapter of HH Book. (For a previous version of the book?)
  Author: Recknagel, Helen
  Recipient: Clark, Jack
- The Founding of a Profession, 6/1981; New Article, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 2, Folder 165)
  Additional description: A draft of a chapter for the book.
- The Founding of A Profession, None; New Article, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 2, Folder 166)
  Additional description: Edited copy of a draft of a chapter for the book
- The Founding of a Profession, Unknown; New Article, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 2, Folder 168)
  Additional description: Chapter of Book
- Black & White Photos, Photo ID's (that don't go with the photos), Various Dates; Photograph, Copy No. of pieces: 12 (Box 2, Folder 169)
- 2 memos stating that anecdotes are needed for the HH Book. Then, 100+ pages of anecdotes>, 11/1/1995; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: Many Pieces (Box 2, Folder 170)
- Rogue Chapter 7 text, 12/1/1995; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 2, Folder 171)
  Additional description: draft of several sidebars
- Colored photos of the Cornell Society of Hotelmen's first Asia Pacific conference, Not Given; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 4 (Box 2, Folder 172)
- Photos of construction being done on Statler, Jun-88; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 42 (Box 2, Folder 173)
- Photos of construction being done on Statler, Jul-88; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 13 (Box 2, Folder 174)
- Construction being done on Statler, Aug-88; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 37 (Box 2, Folder 175)
- Construction on Statler, Aug-88; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 38 (Box 2, Folder 176)
- Construction being done on Statler, Aug-88; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 27 (Box 2, Folder 177)
- Construction on Statler, Aug-88; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 38 (Box 2, Folder 178)
- Construction on Statler, Sep-88; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 35 (Box 2, Folder 179)
- Construction on Statler, Jun-88; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 35 (Box 3, Folder 180)
- Christmas Party, Dec-88; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 27 (Box 3, Folder 181)
- Group office photos, 1988; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 15 (Box 3, Folder 182)
- Christmas Party, Dec-88; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 12 (Box 3, Folder 183)
- Construction on Statler, Jul-88; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 35 (Box 3, Folder 184)
- Construction on Statler, Aug-88; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 20 (Box 3, Folder 185)
- Construction BBQ, Aug-88; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 34 (Box 3, Folder 186)
- Construction on Statler, Aug-88; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 34 (Box 3, Folder 187)
- Ramada Christmas Party, Dec-88; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 24 (Box 3, Folder 188)
- Construction on Statler, Jun-88; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 34 (Box 3, Folder 189)
- Construction on Statler, Aug-88; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 24 (Box 3, Folder 190)
- Construction on Statler, Jun-88; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 34 (Box 3, Folder 191)
- Ramada Christmas party, 12/081988; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 24 (Box 3, Folder 192)
- Construction on Statler, Aug-88; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 38 (Box 3, Folder 193)
- Ramada Christmas Party, 12/8/1988; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 24 (Box 3, Folder 194)
- A global player in hospitality, 11/30/1995; Book, Copy No. of pieces: Many (Box 3, Folder 195)
  Additional description: Several photocopied chapters in the book
- Several old photos, Various; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: Various (Box 3, Folder 196)
- "Ezra Cornell", 05/07/1926; Pamphlet, Original No. of pieces: 3 (Box 3, Folder 197)
  Additional description: Old invitation to the opening dinner of "Ezra Cornell" and menu for dinner
  Author: Student in Hotel Administration
  Recipient: Whom it may concern
- Black & White And Colored Photos, Various; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: Many (Box 3, Folder 198)
- News Articles about the "Ezra Cornell" dinner and dance; 2 transparencies of Dean Clark on new Atrium stairs, 5/7/1926; New Article, Original No. of pieces: 3 (Box 3, Folder 199)
- Negatives of Statler kitchen, None; Photograph, Copy No. of pieces: 4 (Box 3, Folder 200)
- Letter suggesting corrections / a couple edited pages of a chapter / some handwritten notes., 11/27/1995; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: 5 (Box 3, Folder 201)
  Author: Penner, Dick
- Several letters sent in regards to chapter 7, 11/22/1995; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 8 (Box 3, Folder 202)
- Several pages of handwritten notes / 1st two pages of chapter 1 / Letter w/ editing suggestions, 8/9/1995; 07/28/1995; 08/06/1995; Letter, Original No. of pieces: 3 (Box 3, Folder 203)
  Author: Unreadable / None / Reed, Bob
  Recipient: Marcham, John / None / Marcham, John
- Chapter 7 of the Hotel School History, 11/22/1995; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 204)
  Additional description: Letter w/ instructions and copy of 4th draft of chapter 7. Hand edited by James Hisle and returned.
  Recipient: Hisle, James
- Chapter 7 of the Hotel School History / the rest, None, 11/22/1995; 11/26/1995; 11/29/1995 / None; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: 4 (Box 3, Folder 205)
  Additional description: Letter w/ instructions and copy of 4th draft of chapter 7. Hand edited by Mike Redlin and returned. / Letter from Unknown person w/ opinion about chapter. / Handwritten note about chapter. / handwritten notes.
  Author: Marcham, John / Unknown / George Bantuvanis / None
  Recipient: Redlin, Mike / Marcham, John / Marcham, John / None
- Various correspondence about the book. / copy of index, Various; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: 8 (Box 3, Folder 206)
- "Royal expectations in Greenwich" / others, 01/10/1996; 01/15/1996; 01/11/1995; 01/10/1996; Memo, Original No. of pieces: 4 (Box 3, Folder 207)
  Additional description: Cost figures / note about book jacket designs / note about book / article about Prince Pavlos w/ Robert Miller underlined
  Author: Bantuvanis, George / Marcham, John / Jane / Unknown
  Recipient: Marcham, John / Chiu, Michael / Marcham, John / None
- Various correspondences, cost figures for publishing the book, Various; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: Many (Box 3, Folder 208)
- Specifications, None; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 209)
  Additional description: Data Sheets for publishing and printing the book
- Photo of the construction of Statler, Various correspondences about the book and chapter 7., Various; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 7 (Box 3, Folder 210)
- Production schedule, book corrections, 1/9/1996; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 11 (Box 3, Folder 211)
  Recipient: Hotel history committee
- Letter to be accompanied w/ final drafts of the last sections of the HH Book, 1/22/1996; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 10 (Box 3, Folder 212)
  Recipient: Hotel History friend
- Various correspondence about the book, Various; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 6 (Box 3, Folder 213)
- "Statler hard to sell on schools for hotels" / others, None; New Article, Copy No. of pieces: 8 (Box 3, Folder 214)
  Additional description: A couple letters, and an article about how Statler was convinced to invest in the Hotel School
  Author: None / Miller, Floyd
  Recipient: n/a
- Interview with Lois Meek and D Brown at the University of New Haven, April 12, 4/12/1995; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 215)
  Additional description: D Brown interviewing Lois Meek
  Author: Brown, Richard
  Recipient: Marcham, John and Brad
- Suggestions for book, 1/19/1996; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 216)
  Author: Wright, Mary
- Hotel School History Book Committee Notes, 10/5/1995; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 217)
  Additional description: Hotel History Notes
- Editorial follow-up to 9/29-30 meeting, 10/1/1995; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 218)
  Additional description: Notes on meeting.
- several correspondence regarding the book. One of note is from Dittman to Chiu saying that the Jack Clark chapter needs to be re-written to shine a more favorable light on Clark and the school., Various; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 5 (Box 3, Folder 219)
- List of names, None; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 220)
- Preface, 7/15/1995; Book, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 221)
  Additional description: Draft 3 of the Preface
  Recipient: HH Book reader
- Chapter Six: "A Bridge Between the Generations", 9/30/1995; Book, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 222)
  Additional description: 4th Draft of chapters 5 and 6 of the book
- Memo w/ notes on revised chapters of HH Book, 09/07/1995; 09/06/1995; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 3, Folder 223)
  Author: Buch, Donald
  Recipient: Chiu, Michael / Withiam, Glenn
- 1st is a note on chapters 1-5 plus an addendum describing the Beck family. / last two are comments on chapter 6, 04/06/1995; 06/12/1995; 06/22/1995; Memo, Original No. of pieces: 3 (Box 3, Folder 224)
  Author: Beck, Robert / Kennedy, Dick / Semmler, Shelley
  Recipient: Marcham, John (all three)
- Beck's comments on chapter 6, 6/15/1995; Letter, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 225)
- "Memorandum of Conversation by Dick Kennedy and George Bantuvanis RE: Don Buch's Letter about History Book / Letter about History Book, 07/20/1995; 07/15/1995; Memo, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 3, Folder 226)
  Additional description: exactly what the title says
  Author: Unknown / Buch, Don
  Recipient: Edmonson, Brad / Chiu, Michael
- Chapter Six: "A Bridge Between the Generations", 9/6/1995; Book, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 228)
  Additional description: 4th Draft of Chapter 6 of HH Book
- Thanks note for contributing critiques of the chapter drafts., 3/14/1995; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 229)
  Recipient: Lattin, Gerald
- Directory of the Cornell Society Of Hotelmen 1922-41, None; Book, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 230)
  Additional description: 2 photocopied pages from the "Historical Review" chapter
  Author: Kish, Alexander (Ed.)
- Corrections on chapter 2 of the book, 5/21/1995; Letter, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 231)
- Critiques of chapter 1 of HH Book, 01/16/1995; 12/06/1994; Memo, Original No. of pieces: 2 (Box 3, Folder 232)
  Author: Munster, Rudolf / Sullivan, Mike
  Recipient: Marcham, John (both)
- Handwritten notes on chapters 2 and 3, None; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 234)
- Handwritten notes on Ch.2, None; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 235)
- Foreword, None; New Article, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 236)
  Additional description: Foreword written by Beck. Attached note from Glenn W. indicates that it may have been written years before and is newly discovered.
- "Ithaca: Tower of Temperance, Haven of Hootch" / None, None; 03/14/1995; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 3, Folder 237)
  Additional description: typed chapter? sidebar? / critique of chapters 1-4
  Author: Apfel, Ira / Keithan, William
  Recipient: None / Kennedy, Richard
- 1st letter is about Wright's contributions to the book. / Second is about sidebars needing more work., 05/25/1995; 05/30/1995; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 3, Folder 238)
  Author: Marcham, John (both)
  Recipient: Wright, Mary / Brad
- "First Of All", None; New Article, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 239)
  Additional description: Calendar of hotel innovations and chapters of a book about Isaiah Rogers and the Astor Hotel
- A couple requests for permission to publish photos from Kroch; a couple letters about changes made; copy of what the dust jacket and flaps will say., Various; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: 5 (Box 3, Folder 240)
- Memo about enclosed handwritten notes regarding the photo captions, 3/31/1995; Memo, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 241)
- Typed notes on criticisms of the book so far from Michael Chiu and Mary Wright. Notes on 6/15 conference call w/ Kennedy and Chiu regarding chapter 7., 6/19/1995; Letter, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 242)
- 1st 3 documents are corrections to chapter 5. 4th is an addendum about the Beck family. 5th is several pages of chapter 5 w/ handwritten corrections., Various; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 5 (Box 3, Folder 243)
  Additional description: 04/06/1995; 04/02/1995; 04/12/1995; Unknown (2)
  Author: Beck, Robert / Lattin, Gerald / Keithan, William / Beck, Robert / None
  Recipient: Marcham, John (1st 3) / Unknown (last 2)
- Additional chapter 1 comments, None; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 244)
- Letters, memos regarding the book. Several letters of thanks to Chiu for sending free copies., several; Memo, Copy No. of pieces: 8 (Box 3, Folder 245)
  Recipient: Various recipients, mostly Michael Chiu
- Suggestions for coverage of Executive Education in the Hotel School history., 12/20/1995; Memo, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 246)
  Author: Butler, Dave
- A letter comparing the cost depending on the size of the book. / book suggestions / response letter about the Announcements section and draft., 03/24/1995; 09/28/1995; 07/22/1995; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 3 (Box 3, Folder 247)
  Author: Marcham, John / Chiu, Michael / Beck, Robert A.
  Recipient: Chiu, Michael; Shellenberger, Susan; Kennedy, Dick; Brown, Dick / Marcham, John / Marcham, John
- Illustrations, 12/1/1995; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 248)
  Additional description: List of illustrations for the book along with handwritten notes about each one
- Letter to committee members about things still needed for the book. / Letter to Phil about corrections from Proof 3 and 4., 1/9/1996; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 3, Folder 249)
  Recipient: Hotel History committee members and readers / Phil
- "Cornell Hotel School Chronology: The first decade to 1930", 12/13/1990; Book, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 250)
  Additional description: Memo and copy of a draft chronology.
  Author: Anne Foster
  Recipient: Sue DeGraba
- "The Founding of A Profession: A History of the School of Hotel Administration at Cornell University", 1986; Book, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 251)
  Additional description: Copy of a book written in 1986 by a faculty member.
- Several correspondences regarding the creation and opening of the Hotel School, Various; Memo, Copy No. of pieces: 5 (Box 3, Folder 253)
- "A History of Cornell", 1962; Book, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 254)
  Additional description: copy of one page of the book that highlights the creation of the Hotel School.
  Author: Bishop, Morris
- Cornell Innkeeper, Nov-50; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 255)
  Additional description: copy of an issue of the Cornell Innkeeper.
- "Chapter 2: Meek, Statler, and 1922-1929", None; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 256)
  Additional description: Outline of Chapter 2